Ma'am, are you still there?
Yes.
What is your location?
I'm in… in my house, and he's…
Ma'am?
Ma'am? What is your location?
Please! Please! No! Please!
Ma'am?
Ma'am!
Ma'am, are you still there?
A normal-sized gun
would've done the exact same job.
Please stop talking.
You're telling me you wouldn't prefer
just a nice, clean overdose?
It's a Tuesday afternoon,
for Christ's sake.
Guys, can we please focus?
We're already running behind. Come on.
Got some protein ready for disposal.
Teeth.
The guy used a gun that size
knowing he was gonna
put a Jackson Pollock on the wall.
All I'm saying is
that's kind of a douche move.
You can't call a dead man a douche.
- Why not?
- Because it's insensitive.
Uh, morning, ma'am.
The inside of the house is clean.
Sorry about that.
Is this… I don't know,
is this funny to you?
You get off
joking about people's tragedies?
No. No, not at all.
Oh, no? So you're just an asshole?
Or do you prefer douche?
Okay, why don't I take you on a walk
to sign off on everything, okay?
After you.
Just want to confirm
that is your current address
- in case we have to get a hold of you.
- Yes.
- Okay, last one.
- Thank you for your help.
You're welcome.
And again,
I apologize for my team's behavior.
We really are sorry for your loss.
Thank you for choosing us.
Let's hope it's a one-off.
Hello?
- Are you sitting down?
- Uh, kind of.
We have an interested financier.
- You're kidding.
- I am beyond busy.
I don't have time for humor.
Oh, my God! Who? When? Where?
Lead investor's
finishing up a deal on the East Coast.
You have a meeting
at the end of the month. 29th, 3:00 p.m.
- Oh, gotta go.
- Bye.
Oh, my God.
Need a ride?
Do guys really think that works?
Oh, no, seriously, like,
"Ah, he whistled at me.
He must be a really nice guy
and, wow, he drives a Toyota?
I gotta jump on that ship right now."
Yeah, maybe.
Well, so you know, I am on my way
to surprise my husband.
- Really?
- Mmm-hmm.
What's the surprise?
Oh, you know, not something insane.
It's just…
I might've found an investor to get
my brick and mortar store running.
Are you serious?
Let's get you home.
- Hi.
I don't know how to say this nicely,
but you're…
You're kinda crowding me
just a little bit.
- You're such a jerk.
- Stop.
Stop trying…
Oh, whoa.
- I'm sorry.
- Easy! Watch the boys.
- It was an accident, I promise.
- Yeah, right.
- Hey.
- What?
Do me a favor.
Don't leave me in the dust, all right?
Shut up.
And, you know,
it's still a maybe. I don't know.
You're too good for this not to work out.
You know that, right?
I can't do this.
How are things
going for you, Kevin?
I'm not even mad anymore.
Honestly, I… I just feel numb.
It's not about the affair,
it's about betrayal.
You give your whole life to somebody
and they're only
giving you half of theirs?
And the whole time, you have no idea.
And how's it going
in the romantic department?
In the aftermath of an affair,
room is made for a new kind of truth.
A new kind of understanding
and communication.
But you cannot sit in ruin,
waiting for it to rebuild itself.
Have you considered
a change of environment?
Uh, of course.
I mean, that would be ideal.
Excellent. The truth of the matter is…
Your first marriage is over.
Can we all agree on that?
- Yeah.
Now you need
to ask yourselves,
would you like to create
a second one together…
And take action?
Make the change.
Give yourselves
the gift of a new environment.
I mean, she's right.
Your first marriage is kinda shot to shit.
What? I'm just being honest…
Which sounds like the missing link here,
so you're welcome.
I'm just terrified
that he's never gonna forgive me.
You fucked up, sure,
but you know, he's not the only victim
in this situation.
I know you won't say this
'cause you'd rather take the blame.
- I'll say it for you.
- Don't.
Your needs weren't being met.
I can't use that as an excuse.
It's not an excuse, it's reality.
Look, I have a deadline here, okay?
I can't go back and forth about this.
- He pulled away from you, Nat.
- Yeah.
Well, I think that
anyone who found their brother
hanging in a closet
would've done the same thing.
- Come on, Natalie.
- Can you just hand me the floral print?
Hey what are you doing home already?
I just finished early today.
Not interrupting anything, am I?
No, no. Not at all.
- Hey, Dani.
- How's it going?
Oh, uh, shit. You know what?
I gotta… I gotta go. I got work stuff.
- I'll text you later.
- Okay.
See you.
Uh, I want to run something past you.
You have a minute?
Are you fucking insane?
No I'm trying to heed the advice
that we've been paying for.
Take a look at the house.
- No, thank you.
- Look.
I talked to the owner.
She's gonna give us a great price.
You already talked to the owner?
Well, yeah.
I'm taking action.
Isn't that what I'm supposed to do?
Why would you talk to someone
about buying a house
before even asking me. That's not...
You don't understand
This place is perfect.
It's disturbing.
I promise you wouldn't be able
to tell what happened there.
I know. I cleaned it, myself.
I don't want to move into a house
where there was a murder-suicide.
It was unfortunate what happened.
Okay. But shit happens every day.
Are you really being
that cavalier about it?
We live in the the 21st century, Natalie.
Wherever we move, there'll be history,
and I'm willing to bet
that it's not gonna be great.
- Domestic abuse, child pornography...
- Please. I don't want to move into a house
where I'm haunted
by the image of someone's brains
being splattered
all over the living room wall.
Well, I don't want to sleep in a bed
where I have to relive my wife
sucking another guy's dick.
You stopped helping yourself.
You dropped out of college.
You wouldn't talk to me.
Let alone go anywhere near me.
I had a moment of weakness,
and I hate myself for that.
But you cannot keep punishing me.
I know.
I'm going to sleep on the couch, okay?
Hey.
It… it has to have a home office.
Okay.
And we're really gonna
have to cut back on our expenses.
At least until this deal goes through.
I can do that.
And you have to go back to college.
Kevin, I can't watch you
throw your life away anymore.
Okay.
Promise me.
I promise.
Okay.
Wow.
Thanks again
for walking through with us.
We know this is not easy for you.
Of course.
Hey what is that, right there?
Oh, remote locks.
There's an app
that you can link your phones to.
Wow! I didn't even know that was a thing.
Yeah, you're going to find
a lot of that stuff here.
Um, there were some technical difficulties
here and there with the cameras.
I… I guess you would
have to call the company to set it up.
As you guys already know,
my brother and his wife
designed everything here,
so you're gonna get
a lot of expensive extras at a low cost.
- Um, guys, wait till you see outside.
- Yeah.
Whoa! I mean it pretty much
speaks for itself.
Wow.
I know that this is not
an ideal situation for anyone,
but this back yard
and the closet space, right?
Look, Claudia,
we're obviously very interested,
but I'll be honest with you.
It's been a rough couple of years.
I know it's not what you offered.
But it's what we can afford.
If you can say yes to that number,
we can sign the paperwork today.
We really need a fresh start.
Please, let's talk about this.
The truth is,
we haven't had a prospective buyer
in months.
I don't know, I guess
people scare off easily these days.
Add another 20k and it's yours.
Yes! Yes!
Oh, my God, you have no idea
how much this means to us.
We're just as happy
to have it off our hands.
And I know that you guys
will be really happy here.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Thank you so much.
Thanks, man.
- Enjoy the house.
- Oh, Robert.
- Oh, my God.
- Yes, we just bought a house.
Well, Odi loves it.
So? It's beautiful, right?
It's something.
So that's where he killed her?
Ugh! So creepy.
Thank you.
Please, I am just
pointing out the obvious.
Nice plot of land.
Perfect for burying murder victims.
Are you, uh, sure this is a good decision?
Just seems like a lot
to go through to get laid, that's all.
Okay, well,
in case you didn't notice
the moving boxes you helped carry in,
it's a little late for that.
As mom or Gandhi would say,
"It's never too late."
Uh, Gandhi never said that,
and mom is an idiot.
You know, that is very harsh,
on both parties.
Dead body!
I called it!
Oh, that is all you.
Oh, Jesus.
- Is that where he pulled her out from?
- Dani, stop!
You know, it's her own fault,
hiding in a closet
instead of using the front door.
What?
All right, come on, you little freak.
Oh! Oh, my God!
I'm so sorry, baby! Are you okay?
I don't know. Is it bleeding?
No. What the hell were you doing?
- I was joking!
- It's not funny!
It's your turn.
I can't hear you. I'm fast asleep.
- No.
- No. No. No, I don't want to.
Okay, okay, okay.
Come on, Odi.
Let's go. Come on. Come on.
Come on, Odi. Inside.
There's nothing left to pee on.
Odi, come on. Let's go.
Odi, come on. You're killing me.
Hey, shh!
All right, fine. Stay. I'm going to bed.
Jesus. What?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Did you just use the bathroom?
No, but Odi did.
He took his sweet-ass time, too.
Kevin, someone is in the bathroom.
What?
Someone came in here
and went to the bathroom.
I thought it was you.
Kevin?
No. There's nobody in here.
That's not possible.
He'd have to be pretty skinny
for me to miss him.
You have to sleep.
It's our first night here.
Don't spook yourself out.
Let's go to bed.
- Fine.
- Thank you.
What the fuck?
I'm not mad about it.
I just didn't pay for it.
So, if it's free, I'll keep it.
What do you mean you can't refund it?
- I didn't order it.
- Have you seen my keys anywhere?
Yeah, it's my name and my address,
but I personally didn't order it.
- Kevin. Kevin, keys.
- I have to call you back.
Hey, where was the last place you had 'em?
My desk, but I've searched
the entire office, and they're not there.
Right. So that's probably not
the last place you had them.
Hmm. You know what?
I never really thought of that.
It's amazing how some people could really
put it into perspective for you.
Hey.
I'm sorry. I'm just… I'm late, and
I slept like shit and I look like shit.
Babe, you look beautiful.
And you are gonna do great today.
Okay, that, truly not what it looks like.
Don't to be ashamed.
It's a magazine.
It's weird, 'cause you have the Internet.
- Can we look for your keys?
- Yes.
Look, I told you,
I already excavated the entire place.
It's not there.
I swear to God I checked there.
Well, maybe God's just having an off day
and he's trying to fuck with you.
- Don't you have some porn to go look at?
- I love you.
I love you, too.
Oh, um, I know you have a crazy day
between work and class,
so I packed your lunch.
It's in the fridge. Blue lid.
Okay. Go on, get lost.
- Bye.
My youngest daughter, God love her,
is an absolute nightmare.
- Thank you.
- Especially when it comes to wardrobe.
The amount of gifts
that I've had to return
could clothe an entire
Third World country.
She's worn three of your samples
in the last week.
I think you have a really good eye
for color, and texture, and quality.
A female entrepreneur.
An intelligent one of that.
Before opening up your own location,
we'd like to establish you
as a brand name.
Is that an offer?
We can have you in anywhere
between 150 and 250 stores
by the end of the season.
Is this the part where I leave
and pretend to think about it,
or can I just accept now?
- No, you can wait.
- No, I would love to.
- Great!
- Thank you.
- Can I hug you?
- Of course.
Thank you so much!
I'm going out of town next week,
but my associate will be handling
the preliminary process.
Okay.
I want you to modernize the structure
using the original foundation.
Guess what? You get to pair up.
Yes. So, look around. Find a partner.
Someone that's probably smarter than you.
You might actually learn something.
Take this seriously.
This is half of your grade.
Don't procrastinate.
Check in with each other.
Meet up at a coffee shop, go to a house.
I don't care. If you need help, email me.
Don't call. I won't answer.
You again?
Yes, me.
I'm stalking you, didn't you know?
Yeah, I kinda figured.
- So, Kevin?
- So, Avery?
Oh, that's a little presumptuous.
Okay, well, we're partners now,
so I have to be able to reach you.
- Thank you for making it super weird.
- There you go.
All right, Kevin, I'll see you in class.
Don't worry, because this is going to be
the single fucking greatest
class project of all time.
- Just saying.
- Okay.
History of mankind.
Uh…
All right, if this is all to show me
Odi's vomit again, I swear...
Okay, shut it. You're ruining the moment.
Oh, my God.
Wow!
- Who's the lucky lady?
- Mmm.
Um, who, me?
- 'Sup?
- "'Sup?"
Never mind.
I'm going to hang with Odi.
At least he appreciates me.
- No, no, no. I appreciate you.
- Yeah, right.
I do.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome. Come here.
I just figured that if they offered you
a deal, we could celebrate,
and if it's wrong and they didn't,
then we can just get drunk.
Forget about it.
- Mmm.
- Ah.
God! You have no idea
how badly I needed that.
I'm proud of you, Nat.
And not just because
you chugged that whole thing.
But you really deserve this.
Kev?
Hey, you okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
It's just, um…
- Just a bad dream.
- Hmm.
You know, I was thinking about tonight.
- Yeah?
- It was really nice.
I missed the way you sound.
Yeah, me, too.
Especially when I do this.
I'm gonna miss you today.
- Oh, really?
- Mmm-hmm.
That's new.
Well, my meeting is done at 5:00,
so I was thinking maybe
we could grab dinner.
Watch a movie.
I wish. I got called on site.
Oh, I thought you were gonna
cut back on your hours.
Yeah, but I'm trying
to get ahead of the expenses.
Just be smart about it.
Hmm. That's new.
You're a jerk. A very beautiful jerk.
Oh, so I've heard.
- Cocky.
- No.
It's just my way of saying
thank you for the note.
What note?
- Kevin Dadich?
- Yeah.
Sign right here, please?
Okay. What exactly am I signing for?
- Um…
- Okay. Here.
- Thank you. Have a nice day.
- Okay.
They racked up $2,000
worth of porn in your bank account?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
A ghost sighting and identity theft
in one day. That's pretty badass.
- It wasn't a ghost.
- What kind of porn is it?
What? I'm just trying to help.
Maybe I know some people who want it.
Unbelievable.
You know, maybe
it's a paranoid hallucination.
I don't know. Think about it.
Pressure of starting a new business,
the stuff with you guys, the new move.
It is kind of a lot at once.
Dude, are you gonna listen to me
or you're just gonna text?
- Oh, no. I'm gonna text.
- Burn.
Are you serious?
- Who's Avery?
- Nobody.
Some cute girl he shouldn't be texting,
but he is anyway.
Stop.
What? Is that not accurate?
Okay. It's all contained in one room.
- Let's get it cleaned up quickly.
- No. Wait a minute.
Who is she? Where did you meet?
And did you touch bathing suit parts?
No, you aging pervert.
We're meeting up later
to work on some class stuff.
- So the sooner we get done...
- Is she cute?
- Yeah!
- I'm not gonna answer that.
Why not?
Because she's cute.
- No. Because it doesn't matter.
- Sounds like karmic retribution.
Yeah, because she's cute.
Just so you guys know,
things between Natalie and I
have been much better lately.
Yeah, like, much better.
- Aside from the paranoid hallucinations.
- Okay, guys, come on, let's go.
But everything else is so much better.
Oh, it's so better.
- Yeah. Nope. Pass.
- Please.
Dani, I don't have time right now.
I have to get ready for a meeting.
Oh, come on. After everything
I helped you with last year?
Really? You're gonna guilt trip me now?
Only because mom is guilt tripping me.
Besides, I already told her
you're hosting dinner.
What?
Dani, the last time
that mom came into town,
we had to check you into rehab.
If you want to have a relationship
with her, do your thing.
Okay? But I decided a long time ago,
I don't wanna deal with it.
I never ask you for anything.
That is definitely not true. Odi,
I have been playing with you all morning.
She's probably gonna go MIA
again after this anyway.
What is so bad about a slightly
painful dinner every few years?
Fine.
You can bring her here, okay?
But that is as much effort
as I'm putting in.
Okay.
Okay, look, I have to get ready
for this meeting, okay?
Goodbye.
Did you get it stuck?
Oh, yeah, right in the middle.
Okay.
Hi, I'm checking in
under Dadich.
Perfect. The other member
of your party just arrived.
Oh, great. Thank you.
- Hey, stranger.
- Nick.
It's good to see you.
Yeah, you, too.
If you wanna just follow me this way.
Uh, yes. Sorry.
I don't mean to be rude,
but actually have a business meeting, so...
Yeah, I know.
Natalie, wait. Just hear me out.
You know I can't be seeing you right now.
- If Kevin finds out about this...
- It's on me. Okay?
You just tell him that you had no idea
and that's the truth.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I knew you wouldn't come.
A heads up would've been nice
before I signed the paperwork.
I know. You have every right to be mad.
I get it.
But you're talented, Natalie.
And I'm not letting you
throw away an opportunity
over whatever happened between us.
It's stupid.
Anne really likes you, okay?
All I did was provide the info. That's it.
Will you come inside?
Take the meeting? Please?
Fine.
Fuck it. I'm going in for another shot.
You want one?
No, I'm good.
You sure? It's a 100% agave.
Yeah. I gotta drive.
Dude, you do realize we have, like,
two solid hours of work ahead of us?
All right. Yeah, I guess
I have to then.
What is that? West Elm?
Uh, close. It's a hand-me-down
from my brother.
Cheers.
So, what about you?
Do you have any siblings, or…
Um… yeah, a brother.
Be honest. Is he…
The good looking one?
He was, actually.
What? And then he got fat?
No, he died.
Oh, my God, dude.
Fuck, I am so sorry.
I am just so insensitive.
- I'm sorry.
- No, you're okay.
If you ever needed someone
to talk to or anything…
So, 30 feet from the load-bearing beam
is the first floor egress.
Is this getting too cerebral for you?
No, uh…
- I think it's just a sinus issue.
- You want some nasal spray?
Um, I'm gonna pass on the used
nasal spray. Thank you, though.
Hey, hey, hey. It's organic.
Clever upsell, but I think I'll live.
I should get home anyway.
All right, I'll walk you out.
Wake up.
Easy. It's just me.
What are you doing sleeping on the couch?
I don't… I don't know.
Come on.
What's wrong?
Kevin, someone was in here.
No, no, I know what you're gonna say.
It was another nightmare.
But it was so vivid. Kevin, I felt it.
Look, the door was locked.
You were passed out down there,
- probably working...
- You're not listening!
It was real, Kevin!
You're calling me a liar.
No. That's what you're choosing to hear.
All right, let's just talk feelings.
Pissed off.
Kevin.
Yeah, I can tell she is pissed.
No. How are you feeling?
Frustrated? I don't know.
Look, my point is, is that we've both been
going through some difficult changes.
We have this dinner with her mother
that neither one of us are
looking forward to.
Maybe all the stress is
an accumulation of these things.
How does that explain what I saw?
Paranoid hallucinations.
No.
We'll not gonna act like this
with each other.
I never thought
you would take a side opposite me.
I'm not!
I'm just trying to think of
every rational explanation, Nat.
I hate seeing you like this.
If I could take this all away and
make it my own, you know I would.
Let's go have a shitty meal with your mom.
Okay.
Jesus Christ, Odi!
Gave me a freakin' heart attack.
Yes, Nat, I fed your dog.
Odi?
Odi.
Nat?
Hey, little guy.
You doing okay?
Okay. I'll give you your space.
Fuck this.
Odi?
Where'd you go?
What the fuck?
Dani?
Dani.
- I'll just check upstairs.
- Mmm-mmm.
Un-fucking-believable.
Let me guess. She's not upstairs.
Well, maybe she went out to
get some last-minute stuff.
She's not the most organized.
I know, but I told her she needed
to be here to feed Odi.
Okay, so we'll feed him now.
Kevin, he's been home alone all day!
Look, I'm sure he's down here somewhere.
Odi?
Odi, come on, bud!
Odi.
Hi, baby. You okay?
You know, I knew she was going to do this.
This is why I don't want to be involved.
She tries to plan
these things with my mom,
and then they get into it,
and I have to clean up the mess.
And it's such bullshit! I just…
I just want her to show up
when she says she's gonna show up.
Don't worry about Dani.
She'll show up. And if she doesn't,
just deal with her when she does.
- Look, Odi is okay.
- Mmm-hmm.
I'm gonna handle dinner.
I just want you to relax. Okay?
Hmm! It is such a trip how America
westernizes these international cuisines.
When I was in China, there was none of
this sweet and sour and General Tso crap.
Yeah. Sorry to drop the takeout
on you, Farrah. Just short on time.
No, no, no!
Thank you, Kevin. It's wonderful.
Interesting. Mmm.
So, I, uh, take it you're
still working on that documentary then?
If you're talking about my life's work,
yes, I'm still working
on that documentary.
"Life's work?"
How's that going, anyway?
- Ah, it's going wonderfully.
- Hmm.
- Joaquin and I...
- Who's Joaquin?
He's my lover.
Right. Is there any more
Szechuan chicken?
Natalie…
If there's something on your mind,
I am opening the door for you
to share it with me.
No, thanks.
I'm allowed to enjoy my life, Natalie.
You know, when I was your age,
I was raising two daughters
and running a home business.
And who funded that business, Mom?
Oh, right, it was dad.
Drinks. Beer? Wine? I'll be right...
Why is it so hard for you to support me?
Well, it's hard to support something
that I've never seen!
You know, I don't have to subject
myself to this kind of harassment.
- Harassment?
- Yes! Harassment!
You're a bully, Natalie.
In fact, it wouldn't surprise me if that's
why your sister decided not to show up!
Uh, I think we all know that's...
No, no, no, no! No, Kevin.
It's fine. I'd like to leave now.
Yeah! Kevin, she'd like to leave now.
Tell Joaquin I said hi.
You know what, sweetheart?
This brooding teen act
is a little outdated.
Well, so is the whole
free-spirited charade.
You should probably think about taking
"I raised two daughters" off your resume,
because you quit that job a long time ago.
That is so unfair! I sacrificed
everything for you and Dani!
Oh, nothing but "I, I, I, I!"
You are such a fucking narcissist!
- I am not!
- You only care about things
that affect you! Honestly, Dani is
probably at her house right now,
relapsing. Shooting up just like she did
the last time you came!
Why would you say that?
All because you rip through our lives
like a goddamn cancerous tornado!
Come on! We gotta go! We gotta go!
You're not welcome here!
What the fuck!
Jon Santos, 19.
Katrina Kanter, 16.
Trey Mahana, 17.
Any or all of 'em look familiar to you?
No. I've never seen
any of these people in my life.
"Unite the White?"
I don't get it. What is that?
One of the kids copied and pasted
this poster onto their Facebook page.
The original source
had your address listed on it.
It calls to recruit
white supremacist members.
You think we did?
I don't know what to think yet.
But I do know it's a crazy time,
and anything goes.
How dumb would you have to be
to put your home address on it?
As dumb as you'd have to be
to post it in the first place.
Okay. Officer Richardson,
I think what Kevin is trying to say is…
That we would never contribute
to something like this…
Ever.
All right.
If that's the case, you should start
thinking about someone you know who would.
We just moved in a couple months ago.
We haven't had time to
meet the people around us.
But what about enemies outside the area?
Anyone who may harbor ill will?
A scorned lover? A vendetta of some kind?
No. No. I mean, I'm at work,
school, or home.
I don't have time for interactions
outside of that right now.
Mrs. Dadich?
Mmm-mmm. No one.
Isn't there a way to
trace back who posted this?
Sure. Absolutely.
If, uh, the original hadn't been deleted.
So that's it? I mean, what do we do?
They think we're running some
sort of goddamn Nazi operation?
- Okay, Kevin...
- They burned the car! Natalie.
Listen, Mr. Dadich,
we are following the trail that we have.
But if there's other information
you have to offer us.
Anything out of the ordinary,
disturbances of some kind?
That would be very helpful.
No, nothing that immediately
comes to mind.
No.
Right.
Well, if something does.
Claudia. Hi. It's Natalie Dadich.
I was just in the neighborhood, and…
These are for you.
Oh! How nice.
All right. Got the ball. Good boy.
Go get it!
Go on! Go get it, Odi!
The ball! Get… get the ball.
Fancy meeting you here.
Hey.
- Here.
- No.
You look tired
and dehydrated. Take it, please?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Mmm. And thanks for meeting me here today.
Between Natalie's family drama,
house, school,
I just needed a normal conversation.
- Happy I can help.
- Mmm.
Your dog sucks at fetch.
Yeah, he does. Horrible.
Here you go.
Obviously what happened
the other night at the house
was just people toying with us,
but there's still just some things that…
I don't know,
they're just… different.
- You wanna know what happened.
- Yeah.
The truth is, I don't know.
Nobody does.
Sure, we know the logistics,
but we don't know why.
Jay could be an asshole.
He was my older brother, and I love him.
I loved him.
When they were living out of state,
Jay wasn't as faithful to to Erin
as he once promised.
As you can imagine,
it didn't go over too well with Erin.
So, she decided to get even.
She had an affair, too?
Some mystery man no one ever heard about.
She never said his name, or who it was.
- So Jay knew about it?
- Eventually.
Thing is, all those women that Jay messed
around with, they were more like trophies,
you know. But Erin…
Erin, she had real feelings. Bang him…
Well, she said it was a one-time thing,
but that bitch was up to something.
Erin designed the house from the ground
up, but Jay paid for everything.
Every single cent, no questions asked.
My brother loved that woman to a fault.
They were getting along better, too.
I don't understand. If they were doing
so much better, then why…
What is your location?
I'm in my house…
Between you and I…
My brother didn't do it.
Sure, he had a temper,
but he wasn't a murderer.
And he certainly wouldn't commit suicide.
And what, all of a sudden,
the cameras are all fucked up?
There was a lot of
little details that just didn't add up.
The cops didn't care about any of that.
It's not like it was a white man's murder.
I didn't know we had company.
Oh. Oh, man.
Please tell me you twisted your ankle
playing with my dog
so I can make fun of you forever.
I think it was a bee.
I think a bee got me.
- A bee got you? A bee?
- Yes. Is it bad? Does it look bad?
- Ah, there it is. Hold on. Hold on.
- Ow!
Got it. Right there.
Oh, it's a big one.
Are you okay, or are we gonna
have to amputate?
Think I'll get a second opinion.
Hey, maybe you should check on Odi.
Odi.
Odi, come here, bud.
- I've never seen him like this.
- I'll get some water.
Natalie. Natalie.
Uh, I'm… I'm so sorry for the intrusion.
No. No, I… I'm sorry for
making you uncomfortable.
Claudia just springs things on me
sometimes. I just…
She runs her mouth a lot.
Normal husband, wife stuff.
You know how it is.
So you're having some…
some problems with the house?
I may have heard a little more
than I was supposed to.
I… I'm sure it's fine.
You know, I think,
given the shock of everything…
Claudia may have acted
a little impulsively.
If you're having trouble with it,
I'd be willing to negotiate with you.
Buy the house back.
Not much less than you paid.
Less?
Yeah, given the issues,
I'm sure that depreciates the value.
Well, thank you for the offer, but, um…
I just don't think we can
take the hit right now.
Sorry for the intrusion.
You and your husband took advantage
of a woman not in her right mind.
All he left her was that house.
And you two swiped it out from under her
like a free meal.
Think about what I said.
Kevin.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, slow down.
What's wrong?
Hi. I'm Avery, Kevin's class partner.
I mentioned that a couple weeks ago.
Right. I must've forgotten.
Well, I'm gonna…
Bye, buddy. Feel better.
Nice to meet you.
- See you in class.
- Yeah. Thanks.
What?
All right, let's get to it.
We ran Odi's blood work.
I'm gonna be honest here.
Between that and his physical,
it doesn't look good.
How not good is it?
His blood contains elements of a powerful
toxin causing his health to deteriorate.
It's usually due to something
the dog accidentally ingested.
But the root of it is that
his heart is giving out on him.
Well, is this something that we can treat?
It'll really just be prolonging the pain.
Take the time you need. Talk about it.
How could you not tell me
something like that?
I just…
I didn't want it to cause any issues.
Well, I'm going to call you out on
your bad judgment there, Nat.
This deal could change everything.
I wasn't in a position to turn it down.
I had already signed the paperwork,
but I swear, I had no idea.
Have you been meeting him?
It's just work.
Whole goddamn city full of people,
and you have to work with him?
Exactly, okay. Have to.
- Look, I don't have a choice.
- Bullshit.
You chose your work…
Over my feelings, over our marriage.
- No, that's not true. It is not like that.
- He's trying to get in your pants.
Isn't that what you said last time?
Yeah.
I remember that pretty fucking clearly.
God damn it, Odi.
Kevin.
- Kevin.
- What?
Someone's at the door.
- I don't hear anything.
- Kevin, I swear to God.
Okay, calm down.
Don't move.
- What the fuck do we do?
- Get your phone ready to call the cops.
My phone's not here.
Kevin, my fucking phone's not here.
Okay. Stay calm.
Kevin. Kevin, don't fucking
leave me up here.
So, after you entered the kitchen,
you didn't hear any other noises?
No open doors, nothing?
And no physical description?
There wasn't anyone there to describe.
Hey, I'm just trying to jog your memory.
Okay, we'll write up a report.
If anything else comes to mind,
feel free to reach out to me directly.
- There is one other thing.
- Nat.
If you could not make me feel
like a lunatic, that would be great.
- I've been having these…
- Nightmares.
- There is this man. He's rail thin, pale.
- In the home?
Yes. I swear to you, I saw him.
He crawled out into my hallway
and then he attacked me.
Right, so you… you had a pale man crawl
into your hallway and attack you?
And you didn't think to report it?
No. Because, like Kevin mentioned, at the
time, I thought it was just nightmares.
But then things, they started disappearing
and reappearing in other places.
There was this tennis ball
that he put on my bed.
Okay, so he put a tennis ball…
On your bed?
No, the tennis ball, it was underneath
my bed and I could not reach it.
So I went to grab something, and when I
came back, he had put it back on my bed.
Okay. Okay.
Tall, pale man, tennis ball, hallway.
Got it.
We'll be in touch.
- Oh, we found your phone in the kitchen.
- Thank you.
I hope you know how insane
that made us just seem.
Okay, you know what, Kevin,
your wife is sitting with the cops,
telling them that she doesn't feel safe,
that I am terrified,
and that's your response?
Someone just vandalized our house, Kevin.
You don't think it's within the realm
of possibility that someone
could be breaking into our house?
Not to move tennis balls
and house keys around. No.
Well, you know what,
let me remind you
that I am not the only one who heard
whatever was in our house tonight,
- okay, so...
- What do you want me to do, Nat?
I don't know, Kevin. We have a house full
of cameras. Maybe that's a good place…
Do you have any idea
how expensive that would be?
My guess would be less than our funerals
whenever someone murders us in our sleep.
Okay, pump the brakes on the melodrama.
What we need to be buying is a new car.
To replace the rental that
we're spending a fortune on.
We can't afford this right now.
So, uh, once you're logged in,
you'll be able to control the locks
from any room in the house.
So, red means locked. Green. Easy as that.
Right now everything's running smoothly.
If you start experiencing
some glitching, give us a call.
If it's a consistent problem,
we might have to replace the whole system.
Excellent.
I asked for a completed sample rack
with 15 additional samples
by the time I got back.
- I know.
- And what?
It's two weeks later
and I have half that.
I know.
As a person, I am empathetic to
the shitstorm that is your life right now.
But as your boss, I warned you
what you would be getting into.
I don't know what to say.
If you had any idea
how embarrassed I am…
I'll give you the extension. One week.
- Understood?
- Yes.
I need to see the woman who was here
in this office when we first met.
That woman had her life together.
I don't know what to tell you, man.
Sounds like you bought a lemon.
You guys saw that house. It's perfect.
- The price we got it for…
- Was apparently way too much.
Whatever. Let's just get this cleaned up
before the sun goes down.
You know, a similar thing
happened to me once.
Met this super cute girl.
Eyes, smile, even had a good personality.
So I sleep with her. I wake up
in the morning with chlamydia.
False advertising all around, man.
- What do you mean?
- What?
You don't wake up with chlamydia.
That's not the point.
No, it is. If you're going to tell
a story like that, facts actually matter.
How do you even know that
she gave you the chlamydia?
Dude.
- Hey.
- Oh.
You're not getting squeamish
on us, are you?
Maybe you're not cut out
for this line of work, Princess.
- You did this.
- I did it?
Yeah. This is why you can't tell stories.
- Do you need me any help? Okay.
- No.
Oh, God.
I'm working as fast as I can, Nick,
but my mother showed up unexpectedly.
I just had to put my dog down.
I know. Um…
Look, Anne's breathing down my neck. So,
is there anything I can help you with?
No, no, no. I'm fine. I have it, okay?
Did I do something to upset you?
I didn't want to bring this up,
especially not right now,
but since we're on the subject of it,
you cannot be sending flowers
to my house, Nick.
Okay. Um…
was I supposed to send flowers?
No, the flowers that you sent.
Me and Kevin got in a huge fight...
Natalie, wait. I…
I didn't send you any flowers.
- Nick, I saw the card. You signed it.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm sorry, you said stay away.
And so I did.
What the hell?
911. What's your emergency?
I think that someone is trying to break
into my house. It's 992, Hallow Park Way.
- What's your first and last name?
- Natalie Dadich.
Please, I need somebody here right now!
- Please!
- We have officers dispatched.
I need you to remain calm.
Keep talking on the phone.
- Okay?
- Okay.
How many intruders are there?
- I… I don't know.
- Are they armed?
I don't know.
Ma'am, are you able to get
to a secure location?
Are they close?
They're on the way, but
I need you to answer my questions.
Ma'am, can you hear me?
Yes. Uh, I'm sorry I…
I made a mistake.
So you don't need an officer?
No, I just… I… I'm so sorry.
We just had a scare earlier this week,
and I'm really on edge.
- You be safe, okay?
- Yeah.
Help.
911. What's your emergency?
I… I need someone here right now!
It's 992 Hallow Park Way.
There's someone in the house.
We got a call for this number and location
stating no assistance was needed.
I changed my fucking mind!
I need someone here now!
- How many intruders are there?
- I don't know how many.
I don't know if they're armed. All I know
is that they're in my house.
Are you able to get to a secure location?
Hey, Nat?
Nat.
How's she doing?
She's doing okay. Pretty bruised up.
May have a slight fracture.
Did you find him?
Not yet.
We're not sleeping here tonight.
The police checked the whole house.
I don't care if they sit in their cars
and wait around all night.
I'm not sleeping after what happened.
You don't believe me.
I believe you saw something.
No. You don't believe that someone
was actually in the house.
What about my phone, Kevin? How do you
explain all the pictures on it, huh?
Maybe your friend, Nick, took 'em.
- Wow, really?
- I said, "Maybe."
Look, you said yourself the timestamps
were all from when you were home alone.
- I'm sleeping in a hotel tonight.
- With what money?
Our credit cards are maxed out.
The mortgage payment's due next week.
Natalie, would you just stop?
If you're seeing him, just tell me.
Mr. Dadich, good to see you again.
Thanks for coming down on short notice.
- I'm just looking for some answers.
- Uh, well, I am right there with you.
So we went through your security footage.
Before we take a look,
I just want to go over your wife's
official statement, if that's okay.
According to police records,
your wife spots the intruder.
She runs upstairs, locks the door,
then, somehow, the intruder
ends up in the room with her.
She goes to run again,
blocked in by a bookcase,
a bookcase, our team concluded, was in
a position inconsistent with her story.
Mr. Dadich, to the best
of your recollection,
is this account consistent with
what you believe to be true?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
At no point does the footage
ever capture another person,
not in the living room,
not in the foyer, not on the staircase.
Mr. Dadich, no one ever enters
or exits the premises
until your wife
throws herself out of the window.
- I'm not making this up.
- I never said that.
It's called fucking subtext, Kevin.
Why else would you ask me
to go back on my medication?
All right, let's just take a moment.
Natalie, I'd like to be clear
that no one in this room
is suggesting
that you're fabricating anything.
Believe me, okay? I know how this sounds,
but I know what I saw. I'm not delusional.
- We never should've moved into that house.
- But we did. So...
So we sell it.
After all the attention
you've drawn to it?
We. I meant, "we've drawn to it."
Yes, we can sell it back
to Claudia and her husband, okay?
I spoke with Robert, and he...
Wait, you spoke to Robert? When?
When when I went to go ask Claudia
for some history on the house.
- Oh, my God.
- Look, it was a valid concern.
Why would you bother them
about being haunted
by who the fuck knows what
in a place where
their family was murdered?
I don't know, Kevin.
Why are you so concerned
with everyone else's feelings but mine?
I don't understand how I'm the bad guy
when all I'm doing is looking out for us.
You don't have any boundaries.
That's your problem.
You do whatever you want.
You don't care how people feel.
Oh, well, what about how I feel, Kevin?
You have never sounded
more like your mother, you know that?
You're such a fucking asshole. Why
would you even say something like that?
Oh, yeah, that's great. Just go ahead
and walk away like you always do
because you're a fucking coward.
Kevin, what are you doing?
Kevin!
Oh, my God. Someone help!
Someone call 911!
Baby, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Someone call 911!
Mrs. Dadich.
He is coherent,
and there are no indications
of any memory loss
or other physical trauma.
- Okay. So, what happened?
- Uh, why don't you have a seat? Please.
Are you aware of something called Nerium?
- No.
- It's a lethal poisoning agent.
And the reason I ask
is because we found traces of it
in your husband's bloodstream.
Now, taken in small doses
over a prolonged period of time,
it can lead to health deteriorations,
ranging from vomiting or muscle weakness
to seizures or arrhythmic heart function,
sometimes mistaken as cardiac arrest.
You have any idea
how that got into his blood?
I wanna see Kevin.
- I can't let that...
- It's my husband.
- What do you mean you can't allow me to...
- I understand that, Mrs. Dadich.
But he's with the authorities right now.
So, why don't you just have a seat?
No, I am
on your side, Natalie.
Well, it doesn't feel like it.
But I'm just trying to understand.
According to
Mr. Dadich's hospital records,
he's been exposed to this substance
for quite some time now.
What? Why would I try
and kill my husband
after working so hard
to rebuild our marriage?
Oh, maybe because this Nick Scott guy
comes back into town.
Oh, my God.
You decide you wanna have a life with him.
Young, stable, handsome.
Also, he's kick-starting your career.
- I love my husband.
- Maybe a chemical imbalance in the brain.
There's footage of you running around
the house
- from an invisible intruder.
- There was someone in my house!
Maybe because you just realized…
Your husband is
never going to forgive you.
Oh, is this you
ending our conversation?
Well, if I'm not under arrest,
I'd like to get back to work now.
By all means.
- How're you feeling?
- Better than yesterday, I guess.
Uh, hey, I was gonna
make us dinner tonight.
Is there anything you want to request?
You know, I've got to work
on the project again.
- With Avery?
- Yeah.
Are you sure that you should be
pushing yourself like that?
You just got out of the hospital.
It's half our grade.
I don't really know that we have a choice.
Plus, we're running behind. I don't wanna
make her lift all the dead weight.
You don't wanna take your lunch?
No, I'm not feeling up to a whole meal.
Start light.
- Bye, Nat.
- Bye.
Hi. Can I help you?
Sor… Sorry, uh…
You're just such a beautiful woman.
I think you have the wrong house.
Oh… you really just like to
get right into things, huh?
I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
Hey, what are you doing?
Chica, you really do
like to put up a fight.
Come here.
Come here. Hey, hey!
I was just kinda hoping
you'd be wearing a dress,
make this a little easier
on me, huh?
Jesus Christ, lady!
What the f…
Don't fight. It's a mistake…
Got some good news for you.
We were able to ID your attacker.
Travis Murray.
Your camera caught him canvassing
the house just before the attack.
We have reason to believe
he's been watching your house
- for quite some time now.
- So what do we do now?
We get a lawyer, press charges?
Uh, well, not exactly.
We aren't actually able
to place him under arrest.
- What?
- There is an investigation
that has dug up some information
relieving Travis of all charges.
What do you mean? He broke into our house.
Robert Sorrentino, the man who sold you
the house in which you currently reside.
- What does he have to do with anything?
- Sorrentino has been taken into custody
just a couple of hours ago.
He admitted to his involvement.
What are you saying? He sent
some stranger to our house to attack her?
Our detectives found an online post
in Travis Murray's search history.
It disclosed
Mrs. Dadich's name
in addition to a photograph
pulled from an online source.
"I prefer to be taken by surprise?"
Yeah. It was an ad
listed under the personals
and intended to portray Mrs. Dadich
as a lonely, unsatisfied housewife
with a fetish for spontaneous,
submissive sex, preferably with strangers.
Luckily, our detectives were able to trace
the IP address directly to Robert.
Robert also admitted to posting
the initial listing
that provoked the vandalism to your house
as well as purchasing
the magazine subscriptions.
Mr. Sorrentino claims
he wasn't trying to inflict harm,
just trying to scare you all,
hoping you'd forfeit the purchase.
He nearly had my wife raped and beaten.
She is so traumatized
she can't sleep in our house.
He poisoned my dog to death and tried
to do the same fucking thing to me!
Hey, well, hold on.
Hold on, Mr. Dadich.
As of now, Mr. Sorrentino denies
ever personally entering the property.
He says he has no knowledge
of the other attacks against your wife
- and has never been exposed to the Nerium.
- No shit.
Of course, he'd fucking deny it.
Fraud is one thing, but attempted murder?
You're just gonna sit on this shit?
Hey, listen, we have our men working
around the clock to get a confession.
We're still holding him on the charges
he's taken responsibility for.
I thought you said
there's some good news.
Well, there is.
Upon questioning him,
we now have reason to believe
he has a certain level of involvement
with the death of the previous homeowners.
- How so?
- Well, unbeknownst to Mrs. Sorrentino,
Robert had accumulated
a significant amount of debt.
Your house, knowingly left to him
by his brother-in-law…
Was the only financial venture
he had going.
I should've listened to you.
I'm sorry.
I was just tricking myself
into believing that
if I just waited it out,
you'd come around.
But you and I both know that you're never
really gonna trust me again…
Not 100%.
I think that we should
talk about separating…
At least for a little while.
This is half your grade.
Don't mess around.
Check in with each other. Check in
with me. I'm here after class.
Some of you already know that.
How much did you
pay for those shoes?
- Oh, you don't wanna know.
- I don't wanna know?
- 'Cause they look just like...
- Kind of obscene, to be honest.
You should answer the phone.
I mean, what's the point?
She made it very clear that
she doesn't want me to come home.
She's your wife.
You should answer the phone.
Hey, it's me.
Um…
I don't even know where to start.
I'm sorry for what I said last night.
I didn't mean it.
I, uh, assume that
you're still at work, but
if you come home soon, I'd really
love to spend some time with you.
I love you. I'll be up. Call me.
I don't get it.
That's the thing about people.
They change their minds…
A lot, actually.
You know, um, we could just
pick this up tomorrow.
Kevin.
Go home.
Jesus Christ, Natalie.
Get it together.
I hate this fucking house.
- Hello?
- Hey, how's it going?
Fine.
- I'm on my way home now.
- Where have you been?
- You told me not to come home. So…
- When?
When you texted me.
Kevin, I didn't text you anything.
I am looking at
my text messages right now.
I… I can screenshot you my thread
if you want.
Hey, how much for the flowers?
- $8.95.
- They're fresh, right?
Absolutely.
My brother?
Yeah, he had a temper,
but he wasn't a murderer.
- She had an affair, too?
- Mmm-hmm.
Some mystery man no one ever heard about.
Erin designed the house
from the ground up.
That bitch was up to something.
Who are you?
The photos…
Is that you?
No, no, no, no! Please, please, please!
I won't scream, I promise!
I just want to talk to you, okay?
She brought you here, didn't she?
Erin?
She wanted you to be here with her.
And you loved her.
After everything that you gave up…
She still chose him, didn't she?
I think it's horrible
that she kept you here.
You didn't deserve that.
You didn't.
No, no, no…
No, no, no, no!
Please, wait, wait, wait!
Let me help you! I wanna help you.
Kill him.
Yeah. I'll help you cover it,
and then we can stay here together.
He doesn't love me anymore.
I'm so tired of being alone.
A little overboard
on the steam, Nat.
Ah, it's the romantic effort
that counts, I guess.
There you are.
I like the sexy scavenger hunt thing.
The bathroom took a hit, though.
Hey, are you asleep?
You're so wet.
Kevin!
I'm so sorry.
I love you so much. I'm so sorry.
It's okay. Come on. Let's go. You're okay.
Thank God!
- Hey.
- Jesus Christ!
Okay!
You cannot scare me like that.
Okay, in my defense, I thought
I'd just come through the front door.
Can you just help me
get this stuff the hell out of here?
You're doing such a good job
that I don't wanna mess it up.
- I still have a knife in my hand.
- Uh-huh.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You just look good.
How do I look?
Okay, and that moment is ruined.
Oh, I thought I made it better.
I should take that.
- And, uh, hey, thanks for the gift.
- Mmm-hmm.
I wasn't gonna keep it, so…
Hey, guys. I checked all the rooms.
Everything's all clear.
Unless you wanna send Dave back in there,
and I honestly wouldn't care
if he came back.
- That's fine.
- I heard that, Garrett.
- That mustache has changed you.
- I know.
- Um, last box?
- Yeah.
- All right, let's do this.
- Oh, my God.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Come here, bud.
Should we all wave goodbye to the house?
Absolutely.
Bye, house.
- They almost died.
- Yeah.